Guide to the Diaries (Miscellaneous) Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Ford, Seabury (1801-1855), Yale Class of 1825, Ms diaries kept while a student at Yale College; eight volumes [numbers three and four wanting]. Includes a biographical essay by Mrs. W.R. Tuttle of Buchanan, Michigan
  - No.8, 1825 March 28-September 12 (Box 26, Folder 373)
- Eschrich, Oswald, Diary and account book of his voyage from Hamburg to New Haven. The accounts refer to his expenditures in New Haven, 1854-1856 (Box 27, Folder 374)
- Morse, Jared K., 1886-1949 Diary, 1908 (Box 27, Folder 375)
- Seymour, Jack M. "Personal diary...", 1948 August 3-September (Box 27, Folder 376)
- Seymour, Jack M. Map of Palestine, 1948 (Folder 28)